Hello friends, I am Nitin Pratap Patel
and I am working as a Deputy Manager in Mansion Bank.
I have seen insurance business there. I have seen
insurance of Cholamandalam, Tata or Zee.
And in this insurance, when the
car is insured in an accident or a claim is made, then
how do you clean the
insurance, I will tell you in the middle of this video.
And which toll free
number is there, how to call it, what all happens, I will
tell you in the middle of this video. Let's start the video.
First of all, I am going to tell you the toll free number in your mobile,
I have to dial
0020, the number which will be registered
on your policy,
so let's dial it. I have dialed it,
my SIM card is registered,
so I am dialing SIM number 1.
[Music]
Press two for Hindi, so we have given
two numbers.
[Music]
Press one because your car is
registered in motor number 1.
[Music]
I am entering my policy number here
and which number is there
now, congratulations, please turn on your internet.
Click on On Daya Web [Prasha] page
Friends, this computer which is speaking,
you have to call this computer, you should
not disconnect the call, the message must have been sent on your mobile
but you should not disconnect the call, this
computer which is speaking will speak twice and
after speaking twice, Sutai Computer
Care customer care person will attend your call and connect, so
friends, this
number has reached the customer care, I have told you
and after this, what will the customer care
ask you, I have given all this information
in the previous video, if you have
not seen that video then go and watch that video, you will
get the link in the description.